<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ComputerScience on Abdullah Siddique</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/computerscience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ComputerScience on Abdullah Siddique</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/computerscience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>6 Weeks of Teaching: A Journey to Remember with Stanford Code in Place</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blogs/linkedin-ai-trends-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blogs/linkedin-ai-trends-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🎓 &lt;strong&gt;6 Weeks of Teaching. A Journey to Remember.&lt;/strong&gt; 🌍&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share that I&amp;rsquo;ve successfully completed my role as a &lt;strong&gt;Section Leader&lt;/strong&gt; for Stanford University: Code In Place 2025. This global initiative brings together thousands of learners and volunteer teachers from around the world to explore computer science. 💻🌐&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-teaching-experience&#34;&gt;The Teaching Experience&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the past 6 weeks, I had the amazing opportunity to teach and mentor a group of dedicated students in their programming journey. Watching them grow each week, solving problems, asking thoughtful questions, and building confidence, was a truly rewarding experience. 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Women&#39;s Day: Honoring the Inspirational Women Who Shaped My Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blogs/womens-day-celebration-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blogs/womens-day-celebration-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Celebrating Women&amp;rsquo;s Day: Honoring the Inspirational Women Who Shaped My Journey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, as we celebrate Women&amp;rsquo;s Day, I want to take a moment to reflect on the incredible women who have played a pivotal role in my academic and professional growth. Each of them has left an indelible mark on my journey, and I&amp;rsquo;m forever grateful for their guidance, support, and inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-mentors-and-inspirations&#34;&gt;My Mentors and Inspirations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🌟 &lt;strong&gt;Mam Wajeeha Azmat&lt;/strong&gt; – When I started my journey at UAF, coming from a medical background, I was filled with doubts—could I really transition into Computer Science? But Mam Wajeeha changed everything. She introduced me to amazing platform &lt;strong&gt;iCodeGuru&lt;/strong&gt; and mentors that help in every step. Her support gave me the confidence to keep going, and I&amp;rsquo;ll always be thankful for that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
